wtso.com 2016-11-01

# Wine At The Best Price Online - One At A Time - 'Til Sold Out

#### Our Commitment to Privacy

WTSO, a division of Ashburn Corp., is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy as a visitor to our website at WTSO.com. We take the issue of privacy very seriously and value the trust you place in us each time you use our services and access this website. This Privacy Statement describes the practices and policies we have put into place to safeguard your personal information that may be gathered and used as you visit our website.

The policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically. If you have any questions about our privacy policies, we encourage you to contact us.

We do not direct the website to, nor do we knowingly collect any personal information from, any persons under the age of twenty-one.

If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Statement, you are not authorized to use this site.

#### Who Is Collecting the Information?

WTSO is collecting information on this website as outlined in this privacy statement.

#### What Information Do We Collect?

Automatic Collection of Information:

If you do nothing during your visit but browse through the website or download information, our system will automatically gather and store certain information about your visit. This information does not identify you personally and is used in an aggregate way to help us improve our website and tell us the number of visitors to our site each day.

Our web server automatically collects and records the following information:

  *  The visitor's IP address
  *  Aggregate information on what pages are accessed
  *  The name and release number of web browser software used
  *  The operating system used
  *  Date and time you access our site
  *  The address of the Web site that linked to us (referrer URL)

Permission-based Collection of Information:

At different places on our site depending upon the feature you use, you may be asked to volunteer personal information such as your name, email, mailing address, and telephone number. With the exception of credit card information, we store this information for marketing purposes and to allow us to fulfill your requests and otherwise provide customer service. This information is protected by SSL encryption.

If you wish to remove, update or correct any information about you that may be in our records, please contact us by sending an e-mail with your request to help@wtso.com.

Financial Information:

WTSO does not maintain or store any credit card data - that information is stored securely with our payment processor.

#### How Do We Use the Information We Collect?

The information we gather automatically and with your permission during your visit to our website is used in the following ways:

  *  Monitor, review, measure, and analyze Web site utilization
  *  Modify and enhance the website
  *  Improve the content and design of our website
  *  Determine the need for new programs and services
  *  Respond to your requests, including fulfilling purchases
  *  Customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor
  *  Monitor and improve our customer service efforts
  *  Study general usage habits and demographic information for our own marketing research purposes
  *  Distribute news and other information requested by web visitors
  *  Notify visitors about updates to our website
  *  Determine the effectiveness of special promotion and marketing programs
  *  Contact consumers for marketing purposes

Notwithstanding anything in this agreement to the contrary, you understand and agree that WTSO may access, preserve and disclose any submitted information or otherwise use information we have received about you: (1) in response to subpoenas, court orders, legal process or when otherwise required by law, or to establish, protect, or exercise our legal rights or defend any legal claims; (2) to protect the rights and property of WTSO or other entity; (3) if we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent or take action regarding unauthorized distribution of a third party's intellectual property, illegal activities, fraud or situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person; (4) to any of our related companies or companies under common control with WTSO; and (5) if WTSO is acquired by or merged with another entity. We may also use information we have received about you to resolve disputes or to investigate problems. We may disclose or access information whenever we believe in good faith that the law so requires or if we consider it necessary to do so to maintain service and improve our website, products and services. Specifically, we may use information such as your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, to manage the WTSO website or to enhance the WTSO website based on the usage pattern data we receive.

From time to time, we may sponsor sweepstakes, contests, other promotions or surveys. Personal information may be required as a condition of participation for purposes of verifying entrants' identities, notifying winners and fulfilling prizes. The information you provide will be added to our marketing databases and used in accordance with the terms herein; you may opt out at any time.

#### With Whom Will the Information Be Shared?

The personally identifiable information gathered during your visit to this website is not shared with any organization for any purpose.

* * *

#### TITLE & OWNERSHIP

Title to, and ownership of, all wine passes from WTSO to the purchaser in the State of New Jersey and the purchaser takes all responsibility for the import of the package from New Jersey to his/her home state. Since we own all of our inventory and therefore arrange for transportation of the wine, WTSO is providing a service to, and acting on behalf of the purchaser. By utilizing this service from WTSO, the purchaser is representing that he/she is acting in a fashion compliant with his/her local and state laws regarding the purchase, transportation, and delivery of wine. By placing an order with WTSO, buyer authorizes WTSO to act on buyer’s behalf to engage a common carrier to deliver buyer’s order. The purchaser represents that he/she has obtained all required permissions, paid all required fees, is working through properly licensed intermediaries, is legally entitled to take possession of wine, is legally entitled to take quantities ordered, and authorizes that he/she is 21 years of age. WTSO makes no representation to the legal rights of anyone to ship or import alcoholic beverages into any state outside of New Jersey.
